Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010
  - Hope (includes letter from Patch Adams), Jan 2002-Jul 2002 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Hope, Sep 2002-Dec 2002 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Hope, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Hope, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Hope, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Hope, 2006-2009, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Hope: "The People Speak" Script, Notes, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1968-1974, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1971-1973, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues: "The Gordon Empire: A Tenant Research Report", 1975 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Human Nature, 1964-1988 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Human Nature, undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Human Nature: Why War? by Albert Einstein and Sigmund Freud (pamphlet), 1933 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights, 1987-1994, undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights: USSR, 1965-1980, undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Human Rights: Various Eastern European Countries - Czechoslovakia, Poland, Yugoslavia, East Germany, 1964-1974, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Ideology, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Ideology: Education, 1969-1988, undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Ideology: Education - Bloom, Allan, 1986-1991, undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Ideology: Political Theory, 1959-1987, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ideology: Political Theory (includes course outline and notes), 1976-1989, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ideology: The University, 1966-1984, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Imperialism, 1965-1981, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Imperialism: "The American Empire and the U.S. Economy" Reprint from The Age of Imperialism by Harry Magdoff, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Imperialism: Economics of Imperialism, 1975-1981, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Imperialism: Exceptionalism, 2008, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Imperialism: Imperial Expansion, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials, 1962-1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials (various articles and essays selected and annotated by Zinn), 1950s, 1960s, 1970s (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Imperialism: Post-World War II, 1975-1979, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Imperialism: Third World (includes lengthy letter from Peace Corps volunteer re: situation in Mali and Ivory Coast), 1974-1980, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - India, 1947-2006, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Indians: The Conquest of America, How the Indian Nations Lost Their Continent by Hans Koning, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Indians: History, 1989-2009, undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Indians: History, Early, 1997, 2000-2005, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Indians: History, Early (research materials - notes, articles), 1976-1978, undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Indians: History - Post-Civil War (research materials - notes, articles), 1953, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Indians: History - Removal (research materials - notes, articles), 1969, 1975, undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1954-1976 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1977-1978, undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Insurgency (Latin America), 1967, 1968, undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2002-2005, undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Irons, Peter, 1971, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - "Just War" (includes E. Haldeman-Julius Little Blue Book 1547 sent to Zinn by Kurt Vonnegut), 1991, 2008, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Kerry, John, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1972- Oct 1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Kissinger, Henry, Nov 1974-2002, undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Kosovo, 1998-2000, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Kropotkin, Peter, 1969, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Labor: Boston's Labor Movement, An Oral History of Work and Union Organizing (The Boston 200 Corporation), 1977 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Labor: "Corporate Strategies and Workers' Lives: The Dow Strike, 1974" by Brady Mikusko, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Labor: History - General, 1978-1997, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Labor: History - Lawrence Strike, 1955-1973, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Labor: Law, 1975-1981 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Labor: Law, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Labor: Law (I), undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Labor: Law (II), undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Labor: Law - Lecture, 1983-1984, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Labor: Tactics, 1969-1976, undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Labor: Work (includes a student paper, "A Working Class Hero: From a Daughter's Perspective"), 1974-1987, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Labor: Workers, 1973-1976, undated (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Labor: Yale University Strike, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Lafferty, James, et al. v. William Rogers, et al. (Zinn one of the plaintiffs), 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Law: Class and Law, 1969-1989, 2005-2006, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court, 1985-1988, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court - Bork, Roberts (nominee); Justices Scalia, Kennedy and Alito, 1986-2006 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court - Chief Justice William Rehnquist, 1982-1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Law: General, 1971-1999, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Law: "Ideology in the Courtroom" by Howard Zinn and Laura Stewart ( New England Law Review), 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Law: International Law, 2003, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Law: Jury Nullification, 1970, 1985, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Law: Justice 1986, 1975-1986, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Law: Law and Justice, 2003-2008, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Law: Law and War, 1961-1985, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Law: The Rule of Law (annotated articles and notes), 1959, 1960, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Law: Sexual Justice and Law, 1980, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Law: Supreme Court Cases, 1992-1995, 2009, undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Law: Wealth and Law, 1967-1985, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Law: Wealth and Law, 1970-1986, undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - "Les Trois Ages du Neoconservatisme" (incomplete), undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Libya: U.S. Deception, 1986, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - LSD and Dirty Tricks, 1975, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - MacDonald, Alex: Howard Zinn Lecture Series, 2006-2009 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Machiavelli, 1963, 1964, 1971, 1988, undated (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Mark, Karl: General, 1975-2000, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Marx, Karl: Hegel, 1975, undated (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Marx, Karl: Views on History and Structure, 1984, undated (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - The 18th Brumaire of Louis Bonaparte, undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - The German Ideology, undated (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - Manuscripts of 1844 - Alienation, 1958-1959, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Marxism: Articles, Bibliographies and Class Syllabi, 1959-2000, undated (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Marxism: Economics, 1975-1984, undated (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Marxism: Existentialism, 1962-1975, undated (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Marxism: General, 1961-1962, undated (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Marxism: The State, 1960-1987, undated (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Marxism: U.S.Culture, 1967, undated (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Massacres, 1976, 1999, undated (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Media, 1989-2005, undated (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Middle East: Israel - Arms Trade and U.S. Aid, 1980-1987, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Middle East: Israel - Occupied Territories, West Bank and Gaza, 1979-2009, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Middle East: Israel and Lebanon - 1982 Invasion and Aftermath, 1981-1997, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict, 1946, 1948, 1982, 1998-2003, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict, 1974-1991, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict - Western Perceptions, 1973, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Moral Development, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - More, Thomas, 1949, 1985, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Multi-Culturalism, 1991-1998, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - The New Left, 1959, 1965, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - The New Left, 1968-1969, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - The New Left: "The New Left, Memorandum Prepared for the Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act and other Internal Security Laws...", 1968 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - The New Left: Notes, undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - New Progressive Parties, 1993, 1994, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - New World Order, 1991-1998 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - New World Order, 1999-2002, undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1994, 2001, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration - General, 1973-1975, 1981, undated (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Corporations, 1966, 1973-1974, undated (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Ford (Gerald R.), After Watergate, 1973-1975, undated (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Resignation and Post-Watergate, 1974-1975, undated (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Apr 1973-May 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Jun 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Aug 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings and notes), 1975, 1992, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - and the Legal System, 1973-1984, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Overview, 1973-1976, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Special Treatment, 1975, 1978, undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Surveillance, 1970, 1973-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Obama, Barack, 2009-2010, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert Case (clippings), 1954 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - "An Oral History": Graduate Thesis, Boston University School of Journalism, by Stephen Coleman, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Organizations: Various (publicity, solicitations and related materials), 1971-2000, undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Paris Commune, undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Paris Commune: The 31 Official Sessions of the Paris Commune (I), undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Paris Commune: The 31 Official Sessions of the Paris Commune (II), undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Paris Commune: Les 31 Seances Officielles de la Commune De Paris (1871), undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Paris: May 1968 - Aftermath, 1968, undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Paris: University of Vincennes - Relocation, 1977-1978, undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Party Tactics: Revisionism and Eurocommunism, 1987, undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Patriotism / Nationalism, 1980-1991, undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Peekskill Concert (Paul Robeson), 1949, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - The Philippines, 1970, undated (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Plato, the Greeks, 1981-1988, undated (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Poetry, 1992, 2002-2005, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Police, 1963-1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Police, 1970-1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Police, 1980-1987 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Police, 1990-2006, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Police: Community Control of Police (includes Washington D.C. proposal), 1968, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Police: Publications - Day of Protest, Night of Violence, the Century City Peace March, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Police: Publications - Law & Disorder, the Chicago Convention and its Aftermath, [1968] (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Police: Publications - The Nation, Special Issue - "The Cops", 1969 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Police: Publications - The Nation, Special Issue - "Law and Order", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Police: Student Papers, 1970-1971, undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Politics: National Politics, 1967-1974, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Politics: The Political System, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Politics: Psychology and Politics, 1955-1980, undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - The Politics of Nonviolent Action by Gene Sharp: Reviews, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Popper, Karl, 1982, undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Posters: Alternative Alphabet, 1998 (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Posters: Boycott Grapes, undated (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Posters: "Esperanza Chiapas", undated (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Posters: Russian Language Poster, undated (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - The Post-Revolutionary State, 1980-1987, undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - The Post-Revolutionary State (clippings), 1968-1990, undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Poverty, 1998. 2001-2003, undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - "President Clinton, A Corporate Offensive and Okinawa Bases" by Daniel B. Schirmer, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Advisors (to Nixon, Kennedy), 1968-1982, undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Prisons, 1963-1971 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Prisons, 1972-1975 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Prisons, 1976-2005 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Prisons, undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Prisons: Alternatives, 1971, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Prisons: Attica (clippings), 1971 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Prisons: Attica (clippings), 1972-1983, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Prisons: Attica - Lecture Materials, 1972-1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Prisons: Attica - Lecture Materials, 1990-1991, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Prisons: Chapter 777 of the Acts of 1972, the Omnibus Corrections Act (MA), 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Prisons: "The Delta Prisons: Punishment for Profit" (Special Report, Southern Regional Council), 1968 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Crafts, Charley, undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Pisa, Ralph A. "Murder One/Death Row" (pp 1-121), undated (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Pisa, Ralph A. "Murder One/Death Row" (pp 122-242), undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Rufo, Ray, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Salah-El, Tiyo Atallah and The Coalition for the Abolition of Prisons, 1997-2001 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Saxe, Susan, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Prisons: Individuals - Snyder, Mitchell, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Prisons: Massachusetts - Charles Street Jail (Suffolk County), 1971-1975, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Prisons: Massachusetts - Norfolk, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Prisons: Massachusetts - Walpole, 1971-1974 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Prisons: Massachusetts - Walpole, 1975-1984, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Prisons: Prisoner Rights, 1978-1985, undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Prisons: Prisoner Writing (various), 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Prisons: Publications - Doing Time, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Prisons: Publications - Inside Out, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Prisons: Publications - Legal News, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Prisons: Publications - Midnight Special, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Prisons: Publications - The Nation, Special Issue "The American Gulag, A Prison-Industrial Complex", 1995 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Prisons: Publications - The Price of Punishment, Prisons in Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Prisons: Publications - "Prisons & Executions, the U.S. Model", Monthly Review Volume 53 Number 3, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Prisons: Publications - The Problem of Prisons by David F. Greenberg, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Prisons: Publications - Statistical Reports of the Commissioner of Correction (Massachusetts) Year Ending Dec 31, 1968, [1969] (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Prisons: Student Paper and Related Correspondence, 1971, undated (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Prisons: Zinn Proposal for Educational Program (at Billerica), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Professionalism, 1965, 1980-1983, undated (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Proudhon, Pierre-Joseph, undated (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Publications: Old Mole, 1968, undated (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Publications: Various, 1962-2003, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Radioactive Fallout and Impact on GIs, 1978-1982, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Reed, John, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Resistance, 1968, 1974, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Resistance, 1970-1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Resistance, 1973-1976, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Resistance, 1982-1990, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Resistance, 1997-2003 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Resistance, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Resistance, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Resistance, 2006-2009 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Resistance, Jul 2006-Dec 2006 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Resistance, Jan 2007-Apr 2007 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Resistance, May 2007-Dec 2007 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Resistance, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Resistance, 2009, undated (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Resistance: Destruction of Files (includes "Milwaukee 14"), 1968-1974, undated (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Resistance: History, 1984-2002, undated (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Resistance: Military, 1972, 1993, undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Resistance: Military, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Resistance: Military, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Resistance: Military, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Resistance: Soviet Bloc, 1968, 1979-1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Resistance: Soviet Bloc, 1985-1989, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Resistance: Taxes, 1972-1974 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Resistance: Women Resisting, 2005, 2006, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1969, 1974-1975, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.: Address, 69th Annual Meeting, American Political Science Association, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Roy, Arundhati, 2001-2004, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti, 1963, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti, 1979, 1986, 1991-2002, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti: Opera Libretto, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti: Zinn Introduction to Boston by Upton Sinclair, 1977-1978, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti: Zinn Notes, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti: Zinn Talk (75th Anniversary Conference, Cambridge), 2002 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - The San Patricios, Documentary Film: Poster, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Secrecy, 1982-1990, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Secrecy: Archivists and Secrecy (includes letter from Norman Cousins), 1970-1983, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Seldes, George: Interview Transcript for Documentary You Can't Print That, with Howard Zinn, [1983] (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Seminar on Social Change (includes notes and reading list), 1972, 1975, undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - South Africa (clippings), 1967, 1982-1985, undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - South Africa: Publications - Anatomy of Apartheid In Southern Africa, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - South Africa: Publications - The Black Sash, 1975-1980 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - South Africa: Publications - The Black Sash, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - South Africa: Publications - The Black Sash, 1984-May 1987 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - South Africa: Publications - The Black Sash, Aug 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - South Africa: Publications - "The Freedom Struggle in South Africa", 1965 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - South Africa: Publications - Pamphlets, 1983-1988 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - South Africa: Publications - South Africa - A Land Divided (includes a large map depicting removals), 1982-1985 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - South Africa: Publications - Various, 1984-1989, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - South Africa: Zinn Visit 1982 - Notes, Clippings, Draft of Speech (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Snake River Alliance, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Spanish American War, 1981, 1998, 1999, 2004, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Stastny, Charles: Dismissal Case, Central Washingon University, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Stevenson, Adlai: Southern Historical Association Meeting, Walter Johnson Paper on Stevenson, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Student Protests: Various, 1965-1970 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Talkin' B.A. Blues; the Life and a Couple of Deaths of Ed Teashack; or, How I Discovered B.U., Met God, and Became an International Figure; a rhyming fiction by George Starbuck, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Teaching and Learning, 1976, 1983-1990, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Terkel, Studs (Zinn notes), undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Terrorism (includes material on Munich Olympics act of terrorism), 1972-2001, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, 1998, Sep 11, 2001-Sep 29, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, Oct 2001-Nov 2001 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, Jan 2002-Apr 2002 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, Jun 2002-Dec 2002 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, 2003-2006 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath, undated (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Barney Frank Statement (Congressional Record) and Letter to Zinn (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Clippings, 2001-2003 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Clippings, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Commentary, Sep 11, 2001-Oct 12, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Commentary, Oct 16, 2001-Oct 31, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Commentary, Nov 2001 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Commentary, Dec 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Terrorism: September 11, 2001 and Aftermath - Commentary, undated (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Thanksgiving, Nov 24, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Thibodeau, David: A Place Called Waco (selection of annotated pages), 1999, undated (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Trials: Anti-Apartheid, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Trials: The Boston Five (Spock, Coffin, Ferber, Goodman and Raskin), 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Trials: Plowshares Actions, 1981-1991, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Trials: Plowshares Actions (includes Zinn testimony), 1982-1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Trials (involving Zinn support): U.S.A. v. Eqbal, Ahmad, et al. (Harrisburg 8), 1971-1972, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): Armstrong, Karl - Bombing of Army Math Center, Madison WI, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): Massachusetts v. Caldeira, Mark, et al. - Testimony Transcript, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): Occupation at University of Massachusetts at Amherst, 1987-1990 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): Searcey, Emory, et al. v. Alonzo Crim, et al. (Atlanta Peace Alliance), 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): U.S.A. v. Berrigan, Philip, et al. (Baltimore 4), 1967 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): U.S.A. v. Berrigan, et al. (Catonsville 9), 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): U.S.A. v. Buckalew, Terry, et al. (Camden 28), 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): U.S.A. v. Buckalew, Terry, et al. (Camden 28) - Retrospective / Film, 2002, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Trials (involving Zinn testimony): U.S.A. v. Lewis, Thomas P. (Transfiguration Plowshares Action), 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 14)